sideshowcollectors.com 2018-12-24

# Sideshow Freaks - Privacy

This site is owned and operated by SideshowCollectors.com AKA “Sideshow Freaks.” Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your online experience satisfying and safe.  
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

**OPTIONAL VOLUNTARY INFORMATION**  
We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

1\. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)  
We may offer a free electronic newsletter to users. SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

2\. Message boards  
Users of the site's Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

3\. "E-mail this to a friend" Service  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

4\. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

5\. Surveys  
SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

Children  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

**USAGE TRACKING**  
When users access SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it. We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. We may use these technologies to collect and store information about your usage of the SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM, including your actions while using the SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, advertisements you have seen, as well as other anonymous, non-personally identifiable information. 

SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may also use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM to personal information obtained from you or a third party.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

**USE OF INFORMATION**  
SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may use any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, forums and drawings. We may send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:   
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Like many other Web sites, SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

• Google Adsense - Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

• Viglink- Please see their disclosure policy here - [Viglink Disclosures](http://www.viglink.com/legal/disclosures/users)

• Panjo- Please see their privacy policy here - [Panjo Privacy Policy](http://panjo.com/privacy)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. 

SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**LINKED WEBSITES OR SERVICES**  
SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM may also be linked to sites or services operated by third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, contests, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM is not responsible for the Privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site.

**LOCATION OF DATA**  
SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM is hosted in the United States. If you are a User located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States. U.S. data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**OPT-OUT POLICY**  
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include: • Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters, if any. • Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.

**SECURITY**  
SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

**YOUR CONSENT**  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM . If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**CONTACT US**  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact SIDESHOWCOLLECTORS.COM via email at 

admin@sideshowcollectors.com

or through Private Message.
